Why? Why?
Do I wanna sleep with you tonight?
Is it 'cause you're hot?
Is it 'cause you're bi and liking guys right now?
I like that for me somehow
I wanna explore it
I'm a tourist
Lead me on, I won't ignore it
I'll go
Crazy
I think I'm a little bit obsessed
'Cause every time you call I fall again
And I get just a little bit depressed
And I like it, I think I like it
Kiss me slow
I don't know if I'm into it
Let's just do it anyways
'Cause I'm falling to pieces
And your pants are falling down
I'm a Virgo, you're a Taurus
Chart says no
Let's just ignore it and go
Crazy
I think I'm a little bit obsessed
With you
'Cause every time you call I fall again
And I get just a little bit depressed
And I like it, I think I like it
I
Wanna make it right
With all of my heart
Tonight
Tonight is the fucking night
Stacy, I think I'm a little bit of
Obsessed
Macy, I think I'm a little bit of
Tracy, I think I'm a little bit obsessed
I'm obsessed
I said Re-Re-Rebecca
I think I'm a little bit obsessed
I said Felicia, Brandy, Marley, and Jess
I said I think I'm a little bit obsessed
Hey, I said
Selena and Rina, Gina and Carly and Haley
You know you're my baby
I'm talking to Melissa
I'm talking to her sister and her cousin and her mom
I'm obsessed with it all
Did I mention Jill? Yeah
'Cause I'm obsessed for real